你好，美丽的人们知道，在上一个视频中，你们学习了如何在手册中搜索特定的关键字。
Hello you beautiful people know in the last video you learn how to search the manual for specific keywords.
打开手册页以及如何阅读，了解如何使用特定命令。
Open up manual pages and how to read them to learn how to use specific commands.
但那段视频里有相当多的东西，有很多东西需要领会。
But there was quite a lot of stuff in that video and a lot to take in.
所以在这段视频中，我们想要给你们一些练习。
So in this video what we want to do is we want to give you some practice.
在这段视频中，我们将看到一个全新的命令，这是我们以前从未见过的
So in this video we're going to take a look at a completely new command that we haven't seen before
我们将学习如何使用它。
and we're going to learn how to use it.
我们要在手册里找一下。
We're going to search the manual for it.
我们将使用手册页中的概要来学习如何使用它。
We're going to learn how to use it using the synopsis in the manual page.
我们将通读一下它的各种选项。
We're going to read through its various options.
我将尝试其中的一些，看看如何定制命令之类的东西。
I'm going to try some of them out and see how you can customize commands and stuff like that.
我们的想法是，这将向您展示如何使用手册独立搜索资料
And the idea is that this is going to show you how to independently search for stuff using the manual
我们要把整个过程放在一起，我们可以把我们学到的所有东西放在一起
we're going to put the whole process together we can take everything we've learned put it all together
并向您展示如何从头开始学习新命令。
and show you how you would learn about a new command from scratch.
这个想法是，你可以独立地搜索新的东西，并了解它是如何工作的，这就是
And the idea is you can have the independence to search for new stuff and learn how it works and that's
真正的价值来自于手册。
really where the value comes from the manual.
不是让人们随意向你展示他们认为很酷的东西，而是能够走出去，
It's not having people randomly show you things that they find cool is being able to go out there and
找到你觉得很酷的东西，并学习如何独立使用它，它可以发挥你的Linux能力
find stuff that you find cool and learn how to use it independently and it can take your Linux abilities
更上一层楼。
to a whole new level.
那么，让我们继续前进，开始学习我们全新的指挥部吧。
So let's go ahead and jump into it and start learning about our brand new command.
好的，我们要做的是查看一个命令，该命令将允许我们列出
OK so what we're going to do is we're going to look at a command that will allow us to list out what
位于也称为目录的文件夹中。
is in a folder also known as a directory.
好的，我们想来，这将列出一个目录的内容。
OK so we want to come and that will list out a directory's contents.
好的。
OK.
现在我们知道了这一点。
So now that we know that.
让我们继续搜索可能可用的内容，因此第一步是搜索可能提供的内容
Let's go ahead and search for what might be available so the first step is to search for what might
在手册中提供，您可能需要多次尝试。
be available in the manual and you might have to try this multiple times.
好的，您可能无法立即获得可用的搜索词，您可能需要尝试不同的词
OK you might not get the search terms available right away you might have to try different words and
不同的关键字，但让我们试一试。
different keywords but let's try that.
那么让我们试试这个类型，男人过来给它k选项，然后我们告诉你我们想要搜索什么
So let's try this type the man come and give it the k option and then we tell what we want to search
为。
for.
现在我要放入引号，列出目录内容。
Now I'm going to put in quotes list directory contents.
好的。
OK.
我把它放在引号里的原因是我想一次性搜索这个搜索词。
And the reason I put it in quotes is because I want to search for this search term in one go.
我不想搜索单词列表，然后搜索单词目录，而不是单词内容。
I don't want to search for the word list then the word directory than the word contents.
我想一次搜索列表目录内容。
I want to search for list directory contents in one go.
好的，一旦我这样做了，我就按Enter键。
OK so once I do that I press enter.
我们开始吧。
And here we go.
我们得到了一些结果。
We get some results.
好的。
OK.
现在，他们似乎几乎都做对了我们想要的事情。
Now they all seem to pretty much do what we want right.
他们似乎都说列出目录内容，但我听到的是我特别要找的那个
They all seem to say list directory contents but the one that I'm specifically looking for I've heard
ABONSE ONLINE是l s命令。
about online is the l s command.
好的，现在我们也会在课程的布局部分使用ls命令，但是
OK now the ls command is one that we will come onto as well in the layout section of the course but
我们可以看到这是一个用户命令，因为它在手册的第一节中。
we can see that it's a user command because it's in the first section of the manual.
所以我们可以使用man 1 LS打开它，但是因为它在第一部分，所以我们必须甚至
So we could open it using MAN 1 LS but because it's in the first section we would have to have even
有一个我们可以打字的，伙计。
have the one we can type man.
我们开始吧。
S And here we go.
ls命令的手册页中的位置。
Where in the manual page for the ls command.
所以我们现在就在顶端。
So there we are now right at the top.
我们可以看到PRESS命令的位置在手册的第一部分，这显然是
We can see the where in the press command is in the first section of the manual which is apparently
用户命令，我们可以看到该命令的名称是ls，它列出了目录内容
user commands and we can see the name of the command is ls and it lists directory contents and that's
从名称部分。
from the name section.
现在看一下概要部分，我们可以看到，如果您键入L S，那么您可以有多个可选的
Now looking at the synopsis section we can see that if you type L S then you can have multiple optional
选项。
options.
我们知道它们是可选的，因为它们被方括号包围，并且您可以拥有多个
We know they're optional because they're surrounded by square brackets and you can have multiple of
因为它们后面有省略号，然后您有多个可选的文件名或路径
them because they've got the ellipsis after it and then you have multiple optional filenames or paths
到目录，并且可以有多个目录，因为我们可以看到圆点。
to directories and can have multiple of those because we can see the dot dot dot.
但是有一件事你可能会注意到，因为其他的都是可选的，对吧。
But the one thing that you might notice is because everything else is optional right.
您实际需要输入的唯一内容是ls命令本身，它将会正常工作。
The only thing you actually need to enter is the ls command itself and it will work.
所以让我们试一试。
So let's try that.
好的，让我们试着看看我们甚至不需要给命令任何输入，所以如果我们按小写
OK let's try and see that we don't even have to give the command any input so if we press lower case
问：退出，我们又回来了。
Q to quit We're back in.
我们正在退出这一切。
We're backing out of it all.
现在，正如我所说，我们需要做的是进入阿拉斯加本身。
Now as I said the thing we need to do is enter the Alaskan itself.
如果我只键入LS，然后按Enter键，它确实列出了我们主目录的所有内容，这些内容
If I just type LS I press enter that it has indeed listed all the contents of our home directory which
是我们当前所在的目录。
is the directory that we're currently in.
那多酷啊。
So how cool.
好的，现在回到手册页，回到主页。
OK now go back in the man page just go back in the main page.
我们可以看到，我们可以使用一大堆选项，我们可以在描述中向下查看
We can see that there's a whole bunch of options that we can use we can look down in the description
部分。
section.
它在这里显示有关默认情况下为当前工作目录文件的列表信息
It says here that list information about the files which is the current working directory by default
按字母顺序对条目进行排序。
sort's entries alphabetically.
如果未指定这些选项或SORT选项，并且LONG选项的强制参数为
If non of these options or the sort option is specified and mandatory arguments to long options are
做空期权也是必填的。
mandatory for short options as well.
好的，那就够公平的了。
OK so that's fair enough.
现在我们有很多不同的选择。
Now we've got loads of different options in here.
好的，有很多这样的人，让我浏览一下这些人。
OK loads of them let me just scroll through loads of them guys.
好的。
OK.
所以记住所有这些是不可能的。
So memorizing all these is just not possible.
好的。
OK.
就是连试都别试。
Just don't even don't even try.
你不可能做到所有这些，即使你做到了，也有成千上万的
You're not going to be able to do all that and even if you did there were thousands and thousands of
Linux命令，所以做所有这些都有点浪费时间。
Linux commands so it's kind of a waste of time to do it all.
这是您需要知道如何有效使用手册页的内容。
This is what you need to know how to use a manual page effectively.
好的。
OK.
有一大堆选择。
There's a whole bunch of options.
我想向你们展示的是l选项，哪个是好的。
One that I might like to show you which is a good one is the l option.
好的。
OK.
当然，现在您可以浏览它们，看看它们都做了些什么。
Now of course you can browse through these and have a look at what they do.
但是你在这里有一个选项，它代表长列表格式(Long Listing Format)。
But you've got the option here which stands for long listing format.
好的。
OK.
所以让我们试一试。
So let's try that.
听起来很酷。
Sounds pretty cool.
让我们看看那是什么意思。
Let's see what that means.
如果我键入ls并赋予其l选项或按Enter键。
If I type ls and give it the l option or press enter.
我们现在看到，所有内容都以更详细的方式列出。
We now see that everything is kind of listed in a much more detailed fashion.
这是前面放的，这是输出。
This was put before and this is the output.
现在，好了，现在我们对文件夹中的内容有了更详细的了解，来解释这意味着什么
Now OK so we've got much more detailed view of what's in our folder now to explain what this means a
课程稍晚一点。
bit later in the course.
但现在，我希望你们能看到发现新命令的过程。
But for now I hope you can see that the process that you might follow for discovering a new command.
好的，我们搜索手册页，浏览了几个选项，我们尝试了一下，也看到了
OK we search for manual pages we browsed a few of the options and we tried them out as well as seeing
如何首先实际使用该命令。
how to actually use the command in the first place.
现在让我们再来看一看。
Now let's let's have another look in.
我们可以看到这有点难读。
We can see that this is a bit it's a bit difficult to read.
也许如果我们再次查看ls命令并向下滚动，我们可以看到还有另一个选项
Perhaps if we look at the ls command again and we scroll down we can see that there's another option
这里被称为仇恨选项，代表人类可读，我想你可以在这里看到，我们有一个简短的
here called the hate option which stands for human readable I guess you can see here we've got a short
表单选项破折号h或人类可读的长表单选项破折号。
form option dash h or a long form option dash dash human readable.
这就是你如何判断一个期权是否有很长的形式，因为它会正确地移动
And this is how you can tell whether whether an option has a long form or not because it will move right
在手册页的旁边。
next to it in the manual page.
好的，您可能想要设置一些具有长表单的选项，而另一些则不是。
OK you may want to set some options have long forms and some don't.
这就是你如何辨别的。
And this is how you can tell.
它说，使用l选项和/或s选项，这将打印人类可读的文件大小。
And it says that with the l option and or the s option this will print human readable sizes of files.
例如1千字节来积分4兆字节、2千兆字节等。
For example one kilobyte to integrate four megabytes two gigabytes etc..
好的，让我们来看看这个。
OK so let's take a look at that here.
这一列这里的这一列实际上是所有文件的大小。
This column this column here is actually all the file sizes.
上面只写着4,000，好的6或8,980，或者随便什么。
And it just says 4000 a nice six or eight thousand nine hundred eighty or whatever it might be.
好的，但是要使其可读，您可以键入LS、破折号L，然后也给它一个选项，我们将
OK but to make that human readable you can type LS dash L and then give it the option as well and we'll
看到了吗。
see that.
现在这么说是因为它是4千字节，8.8千字节，以此类推。
Now it's said because it's four kilobytes eight point eight kilobytes and so on and so on.
好的。
OK.
而且，因为我们有一个很长的表单选项，而且我们不必只键入嘿，我们可以键入page
But as well because we have a long form option and we don't have to just type hey we might type page
但我们也可以输入人类可读的破折号。
but we could also type dash dash human readable.
我想是这样的。
I think it was like that.
让我检查一下我是否打字。
Let me check if I type.
它是DASH DASH人类可读的吗。
LS It's dash dash human human readable.
我是Pop-Pop，我很抱歉，人类的Dasch是可读的。
I'm Pop-Pop I apologize human Dasch readable.
好的。
OK.
我们走吧。
And there we go.
现在我们得到的输出和你之前说的完全一样。
Now we've got exactly the same output that we have before you say.
您可以在这里看到我们使用长格式选项的方式，这意味着现在我们知道它更易于阅读
So you can see here the way we use a long form option which means now we know it's a bit easier to read
什么。
what.
嗯，你知道那意味着什么，而不是仅仅看到仇恨意味着什么。
Well you know what that means than it is to just see what hate means.
好的。
OK.
但这会使命令更难键入，因此需要权衡一下。
But it kind of makes the command a bit more difficult to type so there's a bit of a tradeoff there.
但是你得到的输出是一样的。
But you get the same output.
好的。
OK.
所以您可以看到阅读手册页实际上是多么有用，如果我们回到ls
So you can see just how useful reading the man pages actually is and if we just go back into the ls
命令并清除屏幕。返回ls命令并向下滚动。
command and be clear the screen go back into the ls command and scroll all the way down.
如果我们一直往下滚动，你会看到一个部分，这是一个很长的手册页，比它要长得多
You will see a section if we we keep scrolling down it's a long manual page much longer than that which
来吧，好的。
come on right.
你会看到一个部分，上面写着，叫做“也请参见”。
You'll see a section that says that is called See also.
好的，这里的这个部分说另请参见它有一个超链接，你可以点击这个超链接
OK so this section here that says See also it's got a hyperlink and you can click on this hyperlink
或手册页中的任何超链接，方法是按住Ctrl键并单击“确定”。
or any hyperlink that's in a manual page by holding the control key and left clicking OK.
现在，如果我们控制左键，如果我右键点击就可以了。
Now if we control the left click that's going to do if I if I clicked it right.
得等一下，我想我们可以走了。
Have to wait I think there we go.
它正在打开。
It's opening up.
所以我点击了很多次，但它在Firefox浏览器中打开了。
So I clicked it multiple times but it's opened up in the Firefox browser.
里面的链接。
The link that was in there.
好的。
OK.
因此，只要您可以访问互联网，它就会为您提供有关该命令的更多信息。
So it's going to give you more information about the command as long as you have internet access.
好的，有时候在手册页上有一些链接，你可以点击，这样就会有另一个链接
OK so that sometimes in manual pages there are there are links that you can click on so there's another
例如，这里就有一个。
one here for example.
这里还有一个。
Another one here.
如果您按住Ctrl键并单击它们，然后您将在浏览器中打开它们，您将能够
If you hold the control key and click them and then you will open up in your browser and you'll be able
看看他们指的是什么。
to see what they're pointing at.
所以这是非常非常有用的。
So that's very very useful.
如果你想要更多的信息，这是你肯定想要做的事情。
And that's something you'll definitely want to do if you want more information.
最后要知道的是，虽然您可以找到关于几乎所有命令的相当多的信息，
And as a final know although you can find pretty much information on pretty much all the commands that
您将永远需要使用手册页，您不可能获得所有的手册页。
you'll ever need using the man pages you can't quite get all of them.
因此，有些命令是直接在shell中定义的，没有手册页。
So some commands are defined directly in the shell and don't have man pages for them.
因此，要查找这些命令，您需要使用help命令而不是man。
So to find those commands you will need to use the help command instead of the man.
赶快。
Come on.
让我给你看看我的意思。
Let me just show you what I mean.
好的。
OK.
例如，其中之一是cd命令，而cd命令是您将一直使用的命令。
So for example one of them is the cd command and the cd command is one you will use all the time.
实际上，它是用来更改目录的。
Actually it's used to change a directory.
您将在课程的下一节中看到这一点。
You'll see this in the next section of the course.
导航文件系统怎么样？
What about navigating the file system.
但是如果我输入mancd，就好像没有手动输入cd命令，但是如果我输入help命令
But if I type man CD it's like there's no manual entry for the cd command but if I type the help command
然后制作CD，然后我们会得到一些非常类似于手册页的内容，我们可以看看如何使用它。
and then do CD we then get something that's very similar to a man page and we can see how to use it.
这里我们得到一个描述。
Here we get a description.
我们得到了选择权，诸如此类。
We get the options and so on.
它类似于OK，所以它的工作方式与手册页基本相同。
It's like OK so it works pretty much just the same as a manual page.
只是您必须使用帮助来查找需要帮助命令才能使用的命令
It's just you have to use help instead to find the commands that are that need the help command to use
如果您只需键入help并按Enter键。
if you just type help and press enter.
你会得到一个很大的清单，这里的每一个都是需要，需要帮助命令
You get a big list and every single one of these in here is need needs the needs the help command to
看到了吧。
see it.
例如，他的CD可以，例如，如果我们在这里做P.W.day，如果我们做man PWT，那么实际上有一个
So for example his CD ok for example if we do P.W. day of here if we do man PWT there actually is a
手册页。
man page for it.
但是，如果其中一个命令没有出现手册页，您只需键入help即可。
But if for one of those commands it didn't come up with a man page you would just type help.
Peter Beattie，它会给出基本相同的结果，就像非常相似的输出。
PETER BEATTIE And it would give you basically the same basic like a very similar kind of output.
因此，如果man不工作，并且您知道该命令是正确的，请使用help命令。
So if man doesn't work and you know the command is correct use the help command instead.
这里还有很多其他的东西，比如在外壳中进行狂野循环
And there's a lot of other things in here like for example doing wild loops in the in the shell for
循环和其他类似的东西。
loops and other things like that.
好的，这是相当先进的东西，更多的是关于外壳，而不是程序
OK so it's it's quite it's quite an advanced thing more about the shell rather than about the programs
安装在您的计算机上的。
that are installed on your computer.
好的。
OK.
所以这只是一件需要牢记在心的事情。
So that's just something to bear in mind.
现在，在ls命令中，我实际上想到了另一件事，请注意，这是有效的
Now another thing that has actually come to my mind in the ls command here notice this is this works
用于几乎所有命令。
for pretty much all commands.
当你有一张很长的表格时，请注意。
Notice when you've got a long form.
例如，当您有一个很长的表格时，几乎所有备份或挡路大小或忽略备份都是这样。
So for example almost all or block size or ignore backups when you have a long form come on like this.
他们往往用破折号把单词分开。
They tend to break up the words with a dash.
好的，忽略破折号备份挡路破折号大小几乎破折号您知道的所有内容都在这里完整的破折号时间组
OK so ignore dash backups block dash size almost dash all all you know down here full dash time group
短划线目录，无短划线组，人短划线可读。
dash directories no dash group Human dash readable.
好的，那么当你做长表选择的时候。
OK so when you're making a long form option.
当我想要你知道人类可读的，而不是像我所犯的错误那样变得人类可读的时候
When I wanted you know the human readable one instead of going human readable like the mistake I made
以前，因为人是一个词，而可读性是另一个词，所以人是可读的。
before because human is one word and readable is another word is going to be human readable.
这就给了我们输出。
And that gives us the output.
好的，这就是关于拼写和诸如此类的事情要牢记在心的事情。
OK so that's just something to bear in mind with regards to spelling and things like that.
但是，当您阅读这些手册页时要记住的主要一点是，每个Linux命令都是专门设计的
But the main thing to remember when you are reading these manual pages is each Linux command is designed
做一件事并且做得非常好。
to do one thing and do it extremely well.
这就是为什么你会有这么多不同选择的LS类型。
That's why you've got a the LS kind with so many different options.
任何您能想象到的与目录外列出内容有关的内容。
Anything that you can possibly imagine to do with listing things out of directories.
LS命令将能够做到这一点。
The LS command is going to be able to do it.
好的。
OK.
这就是为什么手册页有很多信息来真正从中获取信息的原因。
So that's why the manual pages have a lot of information to really get the information out of that.
不幸的是，如果您想成为ls命令的大师，或者您知道，甚至只需开始使用任何
Unfortunately if you want to become a master of the ls command or you know even just start using any
新命令阅读没有捷径可走。
new command there's going to be no shortcut to reading.
不幸的是，我希望有。
Unfortunately I wish there was.
你可以略读，有时他们会给你快速的介绍和命令的快速入门，比如
You can skim read and sometimes they give you quick intros and quick starts to commands and things like
在手册页上，但是对于所有这些选项，如果你想学习它，你必须阅读
that in the manual pages but for all these options if you want to learn it you're going to have to read
它。
it.
好的，所以没有其他办法可以绕过这一点。
OK so there's no other way around that.
所以这就是你将要经历的，你会了解到一个新的命令。
So that's how you will go through and you'll learn about a new command.
所以让我们快速地接连做一次。
So let's do it really quick in quick succession.
我们想了解一个命令，该命令向您显示如何定向您的内容，因此我们将man与
We wanted to learn about a command that shows you how to direct your content so we use man with the
k选项列出目录内容。
k option list directory contents.
它想出了一些可能的页面名称。
It came up with some possible page names.
他们所在的部分和解释。
The sections they were in and the explanations.
ls命令引起了我们的注意，我们注意到它在第一部分。
The ls command caught our eye we noticed it was in the first section.
所以我们只需键入man ls并给出我们看到的手册页，是的，它列出了我们看到的目录内容
So we just typed man ls and gave us the manual page we saw that yes it lists directory contents we see
一个简单的描述，我们了解了如何使用它。
a quick description and we saw how to use it.
您必须键入ls命令。
You have to type the ls command.
这些选项是可选的，您可以有多个选项，文件也是可选的，您可以
The options are optional you can have multiple of those and the files are optional and you can have
多倍于此。
multiple of those.
我们看到，实际上您只需键入ls命令，就会得到一些输出，但是有很多输出
So we saw that actually you can just type the ls command and you get some output but there are plenty
其他选择。
of other options.
这里有很多东西。
There's loads of things in here.
有一件事我们很喜欢，那就是你可以有一个长形式的选择。
One thing that we liked was the idea that you could have a long form option.
好的，长格式选项，我们找到了它，而它在下面，我们在L下面找到它，使用一个长列表
OK so the long form option we found it whereas it's down here we found it under L use a long listing
格式化。
format.
所以我们得看看这个。
So we had to look at that.
我们做的很多，我们有很多。
We do ls dat L We got lot.
我们还看到，您也可以有长表单选项。
We also saw that you can have long form options as well.
好的。
OK.
另一件事是，您可以看到这里有一个小写字母，它为您提供了一个选项和一个大写字母
One other thing is that you can see here there's a lower case which gives you one option and uppercase
这给了你另一个选择。
which gives you another option.
在这里，当你有一个小写字母时，b给你一个选项，而大写字母B给你另一个选项。
And here while you've got a lower case b gives you one option an uppercase B gives you another option.
这很常见。
That's very common.
因此，您需要确保在Linux中拼写时大小写正确。
So you need to make sure that when you are spelling things in Linux you get the case correct.
举个例子，阿纳斯塔西亚会给我们这个。
So for example Anastacia will give us that.
但如果我真的用大写字母L开头，我什么都没做。
But if I do start capital L I didn't even do anything.
好的。
OK.
所以你需要确保你把这些东西都弄对了，只是出于好奇，首都是什么
So you need to make sure that you get that stuff right and just just for curiosity what does the capital
我说如果有大写的L选项。
L say if there is a capital L option.
是的，当显示为符号链接而迷恋信息时，会取消引用。
Yeah dereference when followed when showing falling for mation for a symbolic link.
因此，链接中的文件信息用于链接引用的文件信息，而不是
So information for the file in the link for information for the file the link references rather than
用于链接本身。
for the link itself.
这就对了。
So there you go.
好的，所以您需要确保您的情况是正确的。
OK so you need to make sure that your case is correct.
拼写必须准确，你有一双非常敏锐的眼睛，不会犯错，并确保你
Things have to be spelt precisely you have a very sharp eye and not make mistakes and make sure you're
做正确的事情，因为这些命令的功能非常强大，可以做很多不同的事情
doing stuff right because the power of these commands is so so powerful they can do so many different
但是您只需要确保您输入的内容是正确的。
things but you just need to make sure that you enter them correctly.
好的。
OK.
所以我们走吧。
So there we go.
这是对这段视频的快速总结，我们在下一段视频中要做的是，实际上
That's a quick summary of this video what we're going to do in the next video is we're going to actually
从手册转到下一步。
be moving on from the manual.
我们将向您展示的是命令如何接受输入并实际给出输出，因为
And what we're going to be showing you is how to how commands take input and actually give output because
Linux命令所做的最强大的事情之一就是将不同的命令训练在一起
one of the most powerful things that Linux commands that you do is to train different commands together
组成超级强大的指挥管道。
to make up super powerful command pipelines.
现在，因为当您可以将它们链接在一起时，每个命令的功能都令人惊叹
Now because each command is amazing at what it does when you can chain them together chain these each
在这些单独的命令中，它的功能令人惊叹，但将它们链接在一起，您可以中断创建
of these separate commands that is amazing what it does but chained them together you can break create
一些非常强大的功能，只需很少的努力。
some incredibly powerful functionality with very little effort.
好的。
OK.
所以我将向你们展示如何做到这一点。
So I'm going to show you how to do that.
但首先，我们需要稍微了解一下命令是如何接受输入和输出的，因此您
But first we need to take a little bit of a look into how commands take input and give output so you
才能真正开始一起建造这些卡潘和管道。
can actually start building together these Capan and pipelines.
你需要了解他们是如何接受所有好东西的输入和输出的。
You need to understand how they take input and give outputs for all that good stuff.
我们将在下一个视频中看到你。
We see you in the next video.